http://www.collectorsfirearms.com/privacy-policy

Brands
ColtSmith & WessonU.S.GermanRemingtonWinchesterBritishFrenchMarlinEnglish
Ground Shipping on all U.S. Online Orders Over $100
Loading... Please wait...
Tel(713)781-1960 FAX (713)781-6407
Toll Free: (877) 214-9327E-mail: info@collectorsfirearms.com
Go to Modern View
Search Our Entire Online Inventory Here:
Search Our Entire Online Inventory Here:
Japanese Swords, Fittings and Firearms
How to BuyReturn PolicyPrivacyTermsSite MapAbout UsContact Us
Privacy Policy
Collectors Firearms is located at:
7626 Westheimer Rd.
Houston, TX 77063 USA
Phone:
+1-713-781-1960
Your privacy is critically important to us.
It is Collectors Firearms' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://collectorsfirearms.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "https://collectorsfirearms.com"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our website, will set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website. Depending on your activities when visiting our website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Collectors Firearms collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Collectors Firearms' purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Collectors Firearms' visitors use its website. From time to time, Collectors Firearms may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Collectors Firearms also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users completing web forms
(such as Email signup form) on https://collectorsfirearms.com. Collectors Firearms only discloses logged in user and IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Collectors Firearms' websites choose to interact with Collectors Firearms in ways that require Collectors Firearms to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Collectors Firearms gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register for an account at https://collectorsfirearms.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Collectors Firearms discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Collectors Firearms' behalf or to provide services available at Collectors Firearms' website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Collectors Firearms' website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Collectors Firearms will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Collectors Firearms discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Collectors Firearms believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Collectors Firearms, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://collectorsfirearms.com and have supplied your email address, Collectors Firearms may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Collectors Firearms and our products. Collectors Firearms takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
Collectors Firearms may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Collectors Firearms may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Collectors Firearms does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Collectors Firearms uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Collectors Firearms uses cookies to help Collectors Firearms identify and track visitors, their usage of https://collectorsfirearms.com, and their website access preferences. Collectors Firearms visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Collectors Firearms' websites, with the drawback that certain features of Collectors Firearms' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Collectors Firearms' use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Collectors Firearms — by purchasing Collectors Firearms' services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Collectors Firearms collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Collectors Firearms. Collectors Firearms does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Collectors Firearms may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Collectors Firearms' sole discretion. Collectors Firearms encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.
7626 Westheimer @ Voss
Houston, Texas 77063
Tel(713)781-1960 FAX (713)781-6407
Toll Free: (877)214-9327E-mail:Contact Us
Free Ground Shipping on all US Online Orders Over $100
Visit the Archives  |
Products by Category
Colt
Sign in or Create an account
7626 Westheimer @ Voss,
Houston, Texas 77063
Loading... Please wait...
Browse theNew Arrivals
Email Signup
Toll Free: (877) 214-9327
|
Email: info@collectorsfirearms.com
Visit the Archives |
Sign in or Create an account
|
Privacy Policy
Collectors Firearms is located at:
7626 Westheimer Rd.
Houston, TX 77063 USA
Phone:
+1-713-781-1960
Your privacy is critically important to us.
It is Collectors Firearms' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://collectorsfirearms.com (hereinafter, "us", "we", or "https://collectorsfirearms.com"). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the website. We have adopted this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.
This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our website, will set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our website. Depending on your activities when visiting our website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Collectors Firearms collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Collectors Firearms' purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Collectors Firearms' visitors use its website. From time to time, Collectors Firearms may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Collectors Firearms also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users completing web forms
(such as Email signup form) on https://collectorsfirearms.com. Collectors Firearms only discloses logged in user and IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Collectors Firearms' websites choose to interact with Collectors Firearms in ways that require Collectors Firearms to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Collectors Firearms gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register for an account at https://collectorsfirearms.com to provide a username and email address.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To External Sites
Our Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Collectors Firearms discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Collectors Firearms' behalf or to provide services available at Collectors Firearms' website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Collectors Firearms' website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Collectors Firearms will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Collectors Firearms discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Collectors Firearms believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Collectors Firearms, third parties or the public at large.
If you are a registered user of https://collectorsfirearms.com and have supplied your email address, Collectors Firearms may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Collectors Firearms and our products. Collectors Firearms takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Aggregated Statistics
Collectors Firearms may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Collectors Firearms may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Collectors Firearms does not disclose your personally-identifying information.
Cookies
To enrich and perfect your online experience, Collectors Firearms uses "Cookies", similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Collectors Firearms uses cookies to help Collectors Firearms identify and track visitors, their usage of https://collectorsfirearms.com, and their website access preferences. Collectors Firearms visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Collectors Firearms' websites, with the drawback that certain features of Collectors Firearms' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Collectors Firearms' use of cookies.
E-commerce
Those who engage in transactions with Collectors Firearms — by purchasing Collectors Firearms' services or products, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Collectors Firearms collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Collectors Firearms. Collectors Firearms does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Collectors Firearms may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Collectors Firearms' sole discretion. Collectors Firearms encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or phone.
You can find us on:
